Everyone loathes a clown.
100 Tears is a horror film directed by Marcus Koch.
After being accused of crimes he did not commit, a lonely circus performer
exacts his revenge on those who unjustly condemned him.
The act sparks something inside of him which he cannot stop and now,
years later, his inner-demons have truly surfaced.
Part urban legend, part tabloid sensationalism...
he is now an unstoppable murderous juggernaut, fueled only by hate.
Christine Greaston, played by Raine Brown.
Mark Webb, played by Joe Davison.
Jennifer Stevenson, played by Georgia Chris.
Luther Edward Baxter / Gurdy the Clown, played by Jack Amos.
Tracy Greaston, played by Leslie Crytzer.
Detective Spaulding, played by Kibwe Dorsey.
100 Tears is a 2007 American independent black comedy slasher film directed
by Marcus Koch and written and co-produced by Joe Davison.
It follows the story of a circus clown going on a murderous
rampage after being wrongfully accused of rape.
The film stars Georgia Chris, Joe Davison (who also produced the film), Jack Amos,
and Raine Brown, and was distributed by Anthem Pictures in 2007.
The film was generally well received by independent horror film
critics and has since garnered a cult following.
The tone is dark.